Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics Office of the Registrar records, 1915-1965.
New York State College of Home Economics Office of the Registrar records
- Contains career information and photographs for the following graduate students in the New York State College of Home Economics
  - Barbara McCandless MS - photo only, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faye McCarty (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - James McCurry MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Janie McDill MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Helen McDonald/MacDonald MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Jean McDonald/Hood MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Frances Ewing McFadden MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Roberta McGraw/Vitols MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Betty Ann McKee/Einset MNS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Marylyn McLaughlin/Gautmann MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Thelma McMillan PhD, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ruth Melchior/Krayn MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Grace Melchor/Johnson MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dorothy Mendelsohn MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Esther Rutherford Metcalf PhD, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Frieda Meyer PhD, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mary-Ellen Michaud/Schmidt MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mary Mies/Stefanac (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Catherine Miller/Goldberg MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - E. Jane Miller/Crosby MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evelyn Miller MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Katherine Stafford Miller MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Martha Showalter Miller MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mary Miller (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Nancy Joan Miller MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Hunter Miller (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Carol Millsom MS and PhD - photo only, 1961, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Edna Mitchell MS (Ed), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Jessie Mize PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Christina Mocheva (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ann Molleson MNS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ann Moore/Klosterman MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Janis Moore/Cross MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Marian Moore PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lenora Moragne MS and PhD, 1959, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Marriett Morgan/Tyler PhD, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Olive Morrill MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anita Elizabeth Morris/Lear MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coral Morris MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rosalyn Morris/Frank MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Franc Hall Morse (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mary Margaret Mueller/Carmichael MS and PhD, 1958, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dorothy Mummery (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Patricia Tapscott Musick/Carr MA and PhD, 1973, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dorothea Nagler/Allen MA, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Margaret Nainie PhD, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Roberta Naylor - photo only (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lois Nelson/Person MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mae Elaine Nelson/Dickson MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mary Ellen Nelson (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gwendolyn Jones Newkirk Ed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Norma Newman/Schunk MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kathryn Newton/Brown MS, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - June Nickerson/Stone MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Marion Niederpruem MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Merrilyn Niederwerfer/Cummings PhD, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sally Noble/Bond?Geddedahl MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Francens Nolan/Miller MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mary Nordman (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Martha Norris, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Saundra Norson/Steadman MS, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Clara Nowlan/Jefferson MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - L. Gertrude Nygren PhD, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Henrietta Nyman/White MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kathleen O'Callaghan MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ursula O'Connor (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sheila Patricia O'Friel (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Edith Olson (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Phyllis Olson MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Osborn MS and PhD, 1956, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Roberta Osborn/Jacklin PhD - photo only, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ruby Osterman MA, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Darlene Overly/Cunningham MFS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Emily Owens/Makley MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bue Pai/Yang MS - photo only, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rebecca Palmer/Derbenwick MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Helen Park/Laidlaw MS, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Eula Patrick/Stafford MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Isabel Patterson (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Anna Payne MS, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Irene Payne PhD - photo only, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Damaris Pease PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dorothy Peck/Smith MS - photo only, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - N. Marie Pentz/Meyer MS (Ed), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Olive Perkins MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mignon Perry PhD, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Elna Petersen/Mayhugh MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nancy Pfafflin MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alice Phillips/Loughry MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Margaret Phillips MS - photo only, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Helen Pilcher/Hall MNS and PhD, 1949, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Margaret Polson MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blaine Porter PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alice Powers/Stein MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Marion Prentice/Kibbe PhD, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Phyllis Preusch/Bowen MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cecile Priest/Sinden MA, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Helene Moore Preister MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth Purdy (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Marion Pyne MS - photo only, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - S. Jane Quakenbush/Emmanuel MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ethel Quinn/Holzappel/Scholes MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Eshida Quraishi/Ali MS and PhD, 1952, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Judith Ramirez/Press MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Haris Ramos MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Helen Rankin MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Marjorie Rankin MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth Ray PhD, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - LaVonne Rector MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Philomena Reddy PhD, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Janet Reed MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Martha Reid/Stetson MS - photo only, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Kathleen Rhodes MS (Ed) and PhD, 1947, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Helen Rice/Walker MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annette Richetta/Reynolds MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Clara Ridder PhD - photo only, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Doris Riley (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Elaine Ringelstein (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Margaret Rintz/Pedersen MA, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Susan Riordan/Reynolds MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Janet Ritchie/Smith MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nena Roberson MS, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Irene Roberts PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Martha Roberts/Ranken MS, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Perrylin Roberts/McKelvie MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Mabel Robinson MS, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Veronica Robinson (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wealthea Rockette/Cox MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Catherine Rockwood - photo only (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Catherine Rohrer/Gross MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ruth Romaine/Van Haitshma MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Mary Roth/Walsh MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Susan Stupp Rothschild (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Katherine Roy PhD, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lorraine Rubak/Smith MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Magdalene Russell/Foster MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Maija Saari (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Florence Sai - photo only (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Jane Sanford/Lewis MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hylda Sravia/de la Calle MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ethel Saxton MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Genevieve Scheier MNS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rita Schindler/Storey MS- photo only, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Doretta Schlaphoff/Hoffman PhD, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Benjamin Schlesginer PhD, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Barbara Schlinkert MS - photo only, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - D. Jane Schoppe MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dorothy Schreiner (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - James Schuh MA, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Carole Schulze MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Donna Scott MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Margaret Sedlak/Anderson MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ursula Seeler/Parobek MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Seger/Lawrence MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth Selke/Hensley MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Janet Selke/How MS - photo only, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Barbara Stoakin Severin MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ho King Shao/Tang MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gary Shaw MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Priscilla Shaw/Van Horn MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Linda Shearer/Nelson MS - photo only, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Elizabeth Sheerer MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ruth Sherlock/Anderson MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Caroline Sherman MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Howard Shevrin MA and PhD, 1951, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Audrey Smith Shively MS (Ed), 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Myrna Shure MS and PhD, 1961, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sandra Sibson/Patterson MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fahmida Siddiqi Prov. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Nartha Simons/French MA, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Maria Singson/del Rosario MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agnes Sinniger MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Marie Skellenger MNS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Louise Skow MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - David Smillie PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Barbara Smith/Whaley MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Katherine Smith (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Leona Brodman Smith MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rose Smith/Morris MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Jancis Smithells MA, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ruth Sneed (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Adaline Snellman/Hsia MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Phyllis Snow PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Barbara Snowman/White MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Jean Snyder MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rosalind Solomon MA, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annabelle Spann/Sherman MS (Ed), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Elizabeth Stafford/Vaughan PhD, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Elizabeth Starkweather PhD, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Elaine Starrett MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Jean Steckle MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marjorie Stee/Waddell PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marilyn Steel/Austenson MS and PhD, 1963, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rose Steidl MS and PhD, 1949, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ann Stein/Hertzendorf MS- photo only, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Margaret Steinmetz/Mosher MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Shelby Mitcham Stephens Ed, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Beth Stevens/Hopf MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alice Stewart MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dorothy Stewart/Miller MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gene Stimart/Beardsley MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dorothy Stockburger/Jacquews MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Veronica Stodols/Saemon MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Clars Storvick PhD, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cayle Stouffer MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Juniata Stram/Hirsch MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marie Straszheim/Reynolds MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mary Jane Strattner PhD, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ann Stroup/Pike MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marie Stupp (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - J. Richard Suchman PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Donald Sullivan MA, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Deanna Suneson/Almeida MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Vimla Swani/Sinha PhD, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mildred Swift MS, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Margery Swisher/Sterling MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mary Anne Symons MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Kathleen Taggart MA, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carmelita Tanjano MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gladys Felton Taylor MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Katherine Taylor/Humphrey (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Crystol Tenborg (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Patricia Tengel MS- photo only, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carolyn Palmer Thomas (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Jessica Thomas/McCall MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Sarah Thomas MS, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mary Thompson/Hurd MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anne Thomson/Kelly MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pinkie Thrift (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Janet Tibbetts/Woodruff MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Frances Tompkins (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Molly Totz MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carlyn Tredwell/Johnson MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - L. May Truman (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Yvonne Tung/Feng MNS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sylvia Turlington/O'Neill MS and PhD, 1951, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Evelyn Turner/Curtiss MS, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Janus Turnley/Bulls MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Valerie Twelves/Gillen MS - photo only, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Janet Tyler/Dennison MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gale Ueland MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Underwood MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Elizabeth Upton PhD, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Doris Urquhart MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Myriake Valassei MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Karen Van Derzee/Bogardus MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kathleen Konynenburg/Kelly MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Catherine Veit/Stevens MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Elizabeth Verney/Isenberg MS - photo only, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Wm. Henry Vernon PhD, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Debrah Vicars/Hogue MS - photo only, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dorothea Vieweg MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dorothy Vinansky/Baker MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sabine von dem Knesebeck/Snavely MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Helen Voorhis/Webster MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Charlotte Wade (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pinkye Wade MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aris Wangsgard/Funk MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Eunice Warner MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Helen Warner/Dersch MS - photo only, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Helen Peavy Washburn (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Carol Waslien MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gladys Wasmuth/Knapp MS, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Barbara Waters/Gregory MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Elizabeth Waters MS (Ed), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ellen Kemp Watson PhD, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mary Watson/Misek MS, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bonny Waye/Chirayath MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Beverly Waverly MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alga Weaver MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Frances Weaver MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Shirley Weber PhD, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ruth Weesner/Eaton MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dolores Werner MA, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mary West/Simpson MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dorothy Westfall/Mahan MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Margaret Whelan/Keenan MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Katherine White/Giacomo MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Marilyn White/Clifford MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Martha White/Graham MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Nell White (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Florence Whitesell/Callaway MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Carolyn Widegren (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Edna Wiggins/Schillar (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dorothy Wilborn/Short MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Norma Jean Wilcox/Booke MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Eleanor Williams PhD - photo only, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lydia Williams/Mussenden MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mary Elizabeth Wines MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Jayne Winters/Fife MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Jason Wittman MS, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Frances Wolff/Nathan MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Angie Worley/Murphy MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Margaret Wotring/Boyd MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Martha Wright/Suter MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Chuan-huan Wu/Cheng MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Suen-i Wu (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Irene Wylie MS - photo only, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Jiunn-yun (Joan) Yen-Yeh MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Carolyn Young/Worthington MS - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Josephine Young (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mary Yu/Yao MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sylvia Yuson/de la Paz PhD, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mary Zaehringer MS and PhD, 1948, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Billa Zamir MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Carol Zillgill/Davey MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rita Zimmerman/Derjue MA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Graduate Student Registrar Cards with Photos
  - A-He (Box 2)
  - Hi-Ro (Box 3)
  - Ru-Z (Box 4)